{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963867315","data":{"timestamp":" 946963867315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 2d1db847-9b81-4565-95d2-dcf91468372a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963867552","data":{"timestamp":" 946963867552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 2d1db847-9b81-4565-95d2-dcf91468372a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963867584","data":{"timestamp":" 946963867584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 2d1db847-9b81-4565-95d2-dcf91468372a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963867660","data":{"timestamp":" 946963867659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 2d1db847-9b81-4565-95d2-dcf91468372a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963964496","data":{"timestamp":" 946963964495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963967382","data":{"timestamp":" 946963967381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963969507","data":{"timestamp":" 946963969507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963970893","data":{"timestamp":" 946963970893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963975194","data":{"timestamp":" 946963975194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963977111","data":{"timestamp":" 946963977111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963985082","data":{"timestamp":" 946963985082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963990186","data":{"timestamp":" 946963990186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946963995992","data":{"timestamp":" 946963995992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964005924","data":{"timestamp":" 946964005923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964008956","data":{"timestamp":" 946964008956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964012473","data":{"timestamp":" 946964012473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964015833","data":{"timestamp":" 946964015833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964018681","data":{"timestamp":" 946964018681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964023878","data":{"timestamp":" 946964023878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964027148","data":{"timestamp":" 946964027148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964032722","data":{"timestamp":" 946964032722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964036722","data":{"timestamp":" 946964036722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964041423","data":{"timestamp":" 946964041423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964046557","data":{"timestamp":" 946964046557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964049896","data":{"timestamp":" 946964049896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964055579","data":{"timestamp":" 946964055579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964060761","data":{"timestamp":" 946964060760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964063855","data":{"timestamp":" 946964063855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964068219","data":{"timestamp":" 946964068218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964073266","data":{"timestamp":" 946964073266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964077729","data":{"timestamp":" 946964077729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964082176","data":{"timestamp":" 946964082176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964090948","data":{"timestamp":" 946964090948"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964093946","data":{"timestamp":" 946964093945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" -"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964100555","data":{"timestamp":" 946964100555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964102610","data":{"timestamp":" 946964102610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964115966","data":{"timestamp":" 946964115966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" e95749ec-eebb-4aa1-b31d-9581e1ac6c22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964136471","data":{"timestamp":" 946964136470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964138954","data":{"timestamp":" 946964138954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964140469","data":{"timestamp":" 946964140469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964140571","data":{"timestamp":" 946964140571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964145647","data":{"timestamp":" 946964145647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964146998","data":{"timestamp":" 946964146998"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964151918","data":{"timestamp":" 946964151918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964152132","data":{"timestamp":" 946964152132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964157116","data":{"timestamp":" 946964157116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964157453","data":{"timestamp":" 946964157453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964162586","data":{"timestamp":" 946964162586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964167140","data":{"timestamp":" 946964167140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964167710","data":{"timestamp":" 946964167710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964172877","data":{"timestamp":" 946964172876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964177018","data":{"timestamp":" 946964177018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964184700","data":{"timestamp":" 946964184700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964188924","data":{"timestamp":" 946964188924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964194047","data":{"timestamp":" 946964194047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964195471","data":{"timestamp":" 946964195471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" ("," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964200708","data":{"timestamp":" 946964200708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" ("," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964203129","data":{"timestamp":" 946964203129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964208309","data":{"timestamp":" 946964208309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964208809","data":{"timestamp":" 946964208809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964211179","data":{"timestamp":" 946964211179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964214193","data":{"timestamp":" 946964214193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964215890","data":{"timestamp":" 946964215889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964221064","data":{"timestamp":" 946964221064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964223173","data":{"timestamp":" 946964223173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964226435","data":{"timestamp":" 946964226435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964230534","data":{"timestamp":" 946964230534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964231606","data":{"timestamp":" 946964231606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964234743","data":{"timestamp":" 946964234743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964236757","data":{"timestamp":" 946964236757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964239823","data":{"timestamp":" 946964239823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964249185","data":{"timestamp":" 946964249185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964250032","data":{"timestamp":" 946964250031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964257126","data":{"timestamp":" 946964257126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" aae68a32-012f-4815-b6db-6df59217754a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964279760","data":{"timestamp":" 946964279760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964284967","data":{"timestamp":" 946964284967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964294458","data":{"timestamp":" 946964294458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964299711","data":{"timestamp":" 946964299711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964304108","data":{"timestamp":" 946964304108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964312027","data":{"timestamp":" 946964312027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964317230","data":{"timestamp":" 946964317230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964323761","data":{"timestamp":" 946964323761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964328304","data":{"timestamp":" 946964328304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964333520","data":{"timestamp":" 946964333520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964341792","data":{"timestamp":" 946964341792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964344782","data":{"timestamp":" 946964344782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964348564","data":{"timestamp":" 946964348564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964354190","data":{"timestamp":" 946964354190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964359165","data":{"timestamp":" 946964359165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964361287","data":{"timestamp":" 946964361287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964365208","data":{"timestamp":" 946964365207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964368518","data":{"timestamp":" 946964368518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964372325","data":{"timestamp":" 946964372325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964375623","data":{"timestamp":" 946964375623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964377960","data":{"timestamp":" 946964377960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964380894","data":{"timestamp":" 946964380894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964384348","data":{"timestamp":" 946964384347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964386063","data":{"timestamp":" 946964386062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964387916","data":{"timestamp":" 946964387916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964389349","data":{"timestamp":" 946964389348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964391321","data":{"timestamp":" 946964391321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964402058","data":{"timestamp":" 946964402058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" b40692e9-1c7a-41ac-bfc1-cb586673b650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964420165","data":{"timestamp":" 946964420165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964423672","data":{"timestamp":" 946964423672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964427565","data":{"timestamp":" 946964427565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964431251","data":{"timestamp":" 946964431250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964435610","data":{"timestamp":" 946964435610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964439150","data":{"timestamp":" 946964439150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964443175","data":{"timestamp":" 946964443175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964446010","data":{"timestamp":" 946964446010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964452040","data":{"timestamp":" 946964452039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964455284","data":{"timestamp":" 946964455283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964458856","data":{"timestamp":" 946964458856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964461429","data":{"timestamp":" 946964461429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964466043","data":{"timestamp":" 946964466042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964468545","data":{"timestamp":" 946964468545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964473516","data":{"timestamp":" 946964473516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964483509","data":{"timestamp":" 946964483508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964487485","data":{"timestamp":" 946964487485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964488153","data":{"timestamp":" 946964488152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964492756","data":{"timestamp":" 946964492756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964495961","data":{"timestamp":" 946964495961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964497169","data":{"timestamp":" 946964497169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964510570","data":{"timestamp":" 946964510568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964516406","data":{"timestamp":" 946964516405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 133e5269-74bd-4d56-ab64-b16e7b33e921"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964538818","data":{"timestamp":" 946964538818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964542555","data":{"timestamp":" 946964542555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964542593","data":{"timestamp":" 946964542593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964545961","data":{"timestamp":" 946964545961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964547705","data":{"timestamp":" 946964547705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964550826","data":{"timestamp":" 946964550826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964551058","data":{"timestamp":" 946964551058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964555996","data":{"timestamp":" 946964555995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964561302","data":{"timestamp":" 946964561302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964562218","data":{"timestamp":" 946964562217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964566116","data":{"timestamp":" 946964566116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964567218","data":{"timestamp":" 946964567218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964571247","data":{"timestamp":" 946964571246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964571362","data":{"timestamp":" 946964571362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964574036","data":{"timestamp":" 946964574036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964576484","data":{"timestamp":" 946964576484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964577954","data":{"timestamp":" 946964577954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964581876","data":{"timestamp":" 946964581876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964585666","data":{"timestamp":" 946964585665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964585898","data":{"timestamp":" 946964585898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964587614","data":{"timestamp":" 946964587614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964589776","data":{"timestamp":" 946964589776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964592785","data":{"timestamp":" 946964592785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964594914","data":{"timestamp":" 946964594914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964597386","data":{"timestamp":" 946964597386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964597952","data":{"timestamp":" 946964597952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964602279","data":{"timestamp":" 946964602279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964602550","data":{"timestamp":" 946964602550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964605184","data":{"timestamp":" 946964605184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964607204","data":{"timestamp":" 946964607204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964610275","data":{"timestamp":" 946964610275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964616435","data":{"timestamp":" 946964616435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964618476","data":{"timestamp":" 946964618476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964626719","data":{"timestamp":" 946964626719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964635279","data":{"timestamp":" 946964635279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 808a9daf-6e1b-4ea3-8133-abff6519a98a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964660027","data":{"timestamp":" 946964660026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964669381","data":{"timestamp":" 946964669381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964669678","data":{"timestamp":" 946964669678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964673735","data":{"timestamp":" 946964673735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964674465","data":{"timestamp":" 946964674465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964677125","data":{"timestamp":" 946964677124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964678810","data":{"timestamp":" 946964678810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964681267","data":{"timestamp":" 946964681267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964684761","data":{"timestamp":" 946964684761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964689012","data":{"timestamp":" 946964689011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964690007","data":{"timestamp":" 946964690007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964695041","data":{"timestamp":" 946964695041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964698233","data":{"timestamp":" 946964698233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964699108","data":{"timestamp":" 946964699107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964701395","data":{"timestamp":" 946964701395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964705890","data":{"timestamp":" 946964705890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964706259","data":{"timestamp":" 946964706258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964708418","data":{"timestamp":" 946964708418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964710983","data":{"timestamp":" 946964710983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964711117","data":{"timestamp":" 946964711117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964715224","data":{"timestamp":" 946964715224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964716219","data":{"timestamp":" 946964716219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964717900","data":{"timestamp":" 946964717900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964720945","data":{"timestamp":" 946964720944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964725698","data":{"timestamp":" 946964725698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964726131","data":{"timestamp":" 946964726131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964730739","data":{"timestamp":" 946964730739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964731192","data":{"timestamp":" 946964731192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964735787","data":{"timestamp":" 946964735787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964737272","data":{"timestamp":" 946964737272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964739874","data":{"timestamp":" 946964739874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964740627","data":{"timestamp":" 946964740627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964745105","data":{"timestamp":" 946964745105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964751827","data":{"timestamp":" 946964751827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964758887","data":{"timestamp":" 946964758887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 1d290293-4dd2-4af6-8421-feb2d39ae44f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964782959","data":{"timestamp":" 946964782959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964785855","data":{"timestamp":" 946964785855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964787291","data":{"timestamp":" 946964787291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964789747","data":{"timestamp":" 946964789747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964792757","data":{"timestamp":" 946964792757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964800779","data":{"timestamp":" 946964800779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964803770","data":{"timestamp":" 946964803770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964809166","data":{"timestamp":" 946964809166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964810437","data":{"timestamp":" 946964810437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964810496","data":{"timestamp":" 946964810496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964820411","data":{"timestamp":" 946964820410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964825838","data":{"timestamp":" 946964825837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964830561","data":{"timestamp":" 946964830561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964835564","data":{"timestamp":" 946964835564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964839424","data":{"timestamp":" 946964839424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964841929","data":{"timestamp":" 946964841929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964844009","data":{"timestamp":" 946964844009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964852455","data":{"timestamp":" 946964852455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964858283","data":{"timestamp":" 946964858283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964867768","data":{"timestamp":" 946964867768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964876529","data":{"timestamp":" 946964876529"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946964883468","data":{"timestamp":" 946964883468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_083055"," gameId":" 9ca62531-6f47-45d0-89f0-010b940ecf1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"end":"end"}]}